Kheel, Theodore W. Arbitration files 6021/003
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Local 447, Int'l Union of electrical Radio and Machine Workers, AFL-CIO, and Federal Telephone and Radio Company, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 121)
- Clerical and Technical Workers, Local 1703, IUE, and Federal Telephone and Radio Company, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Clerical Technical Workers, Local 1703, IUE, and Federal Telephone and Radio Company Angelo Massaro, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Clerical and Technical Workers, Local 1703, IUE, and Federal Telephone and Radio Co., 1957 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Clerical and Technical Workers, Local 1703, IUE, and Federal Telephone and Radio Co. L Gingerelli, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Clerical and Technical Workers, Local 1703, IUE, and Federal Telephone and Radio Co. Miss E. Shadel, et al., 1957 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Clerical and Technical Workers, Local 1703, IUE, and Federal Telephone and Radio Co. T Gaglione, et al., 1958 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Union of electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 1703, IUE, and Federal Telephone and Radio Co., 1958 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Brewery Decisions (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Leather Goods, Plastics, Handbags and Novelty Workers Union, Local, 1 and A&M Leather Lines, Inc., 1978 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Leather Goods, Plastics Handbags and Novelty Workers Union, Local 1, and A&M Leather Lines, Inc. Eleuterio Soto, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Leather Goods, Plastics, Handbags and Novelty Workers Union, Local 1, and AFM Leatherlines, Inc., 1983 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Leather Goods, Plastics, Handbags and Novelty Workers Union, Local 1, and Adam Artistic Acessories Limited, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Leather goods, Plastics, Handbags and Novelty Workers Union, Local 1, and Adam Artistic Accessories, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Leather goods, Plastics, Handbags, and Novelty Workers Union, Local 1, and Art Craft Wallets, Inc. Porfirio Rosario, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Leather goods, Plastics, Handbags, and Novelty Workers Union, Local 1 and Bell Handbags, Inc., 1981 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Leather goods, Plastics, Handbags, and Novelty Workers Union, Local 1, and Jerome Blecker d/b/a M&M Originals and Jerome Blecker Co., 1983 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Leather goods, Plastics, Handbags and novelty Workers Union, Local 11, and Block Handbag, Inc., 1983 (Box 24, Folder 17)
- Leather Goods, Plastics, Handbags and Novelty workers Union, Local 11 and Borgzinner, Inc. Mercedes Cebollero, et al., 1983 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Leather Goods, Plastics, Handbags and Novelty workers Union, Local 11 and Carter Leather Goods, Inc. Vincent Mazzella, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- Leather Goods, Plastics, Handbags and Novelty workers Union, Local 11 and carter Leather Goods, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 20)
- Leather Goods, Plastics, Handbags and Novelty workers Union, Local 11 and Celebrity, Inc. Jose Arryo, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  Dec 24
- Leather Goods, Plastics, Handbags and Novelty workers Union, Local 11 and Century Needleworks, Inc., 1981 (Box 24, Folder 22)
- Leather Goods, Plastics, Handbags and Novelty workers Union, Local 11 and Century Needleworks, Inc., 1983 (Box 24, Folder 23)
- Leather Goods, Plastics, Handbags and Novelty workers Union, Local 11 and Chic De Paris Handbag Corp., 1983 (Box 24, Folder 24)
- Leather Goods, Plastics, Handbags and Novelty workers Union, Local 11, and Chic De Paris Handbag Corp., 1983 (Box 24, Folder 25)
- Leather Goods, Plastics, Handbags and Novelty workers Union, Local, and coach Products Manuel Evans, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 26)
- Leather Goods, Plastics, Handbags and Novelty workers Union, Local 11, and colonial Novelties, Inc., 1983 (Box 24, Folder 27)
- Leather Goods, Plastics, Handbags and Novelty workers Union, Local 11, and Evans Aristocrat, Inc., 1981 (Box 24, Folder 28)
- Leather Goods, Plastics, Handbags and Novelty workers Union, Local 1, and Evans Aristocrat, Inc., 1982 (Box 24, Folder 29)
- Leather Goods, Plastics, Handbags and Novelty workers Union, Local 11, and Fabric Leather corp., 1983 (Box 24, Folder 30)
- Leather Goods, Plastics, Handbags and Novelty workers Union, Local 1, and Fancy industries, Inc., 1981 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  May 27
- Leather Goods, Plastics, Handbags and Novelty workers Union, Local 1, and Fancy Industries, Inc., 1981 (Box 24, Folder 32)
- Leather Goods, Plastics, Handbags and Novelty workers Union, Local 1, and Flower Handbag corp., 1981 (Box 24, Folder 33)
- Leather Goods, Plastics, Handbags and Novelty workers Union, Local 1, and Flower Handbag Corp., 1982 (Box 24, Folder 34)
- Leather Goods, Plastics, Handbags and Novelty workers Union, Local 1, and Flower Handbag corp., 1983 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  Aug 29
- Leather Goods, Plastics, Handbags and Novelty workers Union, Local 1, and Fordham Repair Center, Inc. Bill Rivera, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 36)
- Leather Goods, Plastics, Handbags and Novelty workers Union, Local 1, and Handbag and Bags by Scobe, Inc., 1979 (Box 24, Folder 37)
- Leather Goods, Plastics, Handbags and Novelty workers Union, Local 1, and Howard Berger co. Inc., 1983 (Box 24, Folder 38)
- Leather Goods, Plastics, Handbags and Novelty workers Union, Local 1, and Jade Handbag, Inc., 1983 (Box 24, Folder 39)
- Leather Goods, Plastics, Handbags and Novelty workers Union, Local 1, and Lewis Purses, Inc., 1983 (Box 24, Folder 40)
- Leather Goods, Plastics, Handbags and Novelty workers Union, Local 1, and M and L Radin co., 1979 (Box 24, Folder 41)
- Leather Goods, Plastics, Handbags and Novelty workers Union, Local 1, and M and L Radin, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 42)
- Leather Goods, Plastics, Handbags and Novelty workers Union, Local 1, and Maxon Leather Goods, Inc., 1981 (Box 24, Folder 43)
- Leather Goods, Plastics, Handbags and Novelty workers Union, Local 1, and Maxam Leather Goods, Inc., 1983 (Box 24, Folder 44)
- Leather Goods, Plastics, Handbags and Novelty workers Union, Local 1, Mormac co. Inc., 1981 (Box 24, Folder 45)
- Leather Goods, Plastics, Handbags and Novelty workers Union, Local 1, and Paris Mode Co., Inc., 1982 (Box 24, Folder 46)
- Leather Goods, Plastics, Handbags and Novelty workers Union, Local 1, and Penmar, Inc., 1983 (Box 24, Folder 47)
- Leather Goods, Plastics, Handbags and Novelty workers Union, Local 1, and Princess Leather Goods, Inc., 1982 (Box 24, Folder 48)
- Leather Goods, Plastics, Handbags and Novelty workers Union, Local 1, and Reliable Handbag, Corp., 1981 (Box 24, Folder 49)
- Leather Goods, Plastics, Handbags and Novelty workers Union, Local 1, and SIRCO Int'l Corp. Thomas Reid, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 50)
  Jan 5
- Leather Goods, Plastics, Handbags and Novelty workers Union, Local 1, and Suzy Handbag Co., 1983 (Box 24, Folder 51)
- Leather Goods, Plastics, Handbags and Novelty workers Union, Local 1, and T. Lisher Co., 1979 (Box 24, Folder 52)
- Leather Goods, Plastics, Handbags and Novelty workers Union, Local 1, and Vance Novelties, Inc., 1983 (Box 24, Folder 53)
- Leather Goods, Plastics, Handbags and Novelty workers Union, Local 1, and Marc Weisstuch d/b/a Princess Leather Goods Mfg. and Empress Products, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 54)
- Leather Goods, Plastics, Handbags and Novelty workers Union, Local 1, and Zenith Handbag corp., 1983 (Box 24, Folder 55)
- Leather Goods, Plastics, Handbags and Novelty workers Union, Local 1, and Celebrity, Inc. Heriberto Morales, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 56)
- Leather Goods, Plastics, Handbags and Novelty workers Union, Local 1, and Chic de Paris Handbag Corp., 1983 (Box 24, Folder 57)
- Leather Goods, Plastics, Handbags and Novelty workers Union, and Pandy Handbag, Co. Carmen Pacheco, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 58)
- Leather Goods, Plastics, Handbags and Novelty workers Union, Local 1, and New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association, and Best Craft Handbag Corp. Fernando Robleto, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Leather Goods, Plastics, Handbags and Novelty workers Union, Local 1, and New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association and Calderon Belts Bags, Inc. Hector Mendez, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  Nov 12
- Leather Goods, Plastics, Handbags and Novelty workers Union, Local 1, and New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association, and Fancy Industries, Inc. Manila Titus, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Leather Goods, Plastics, Handbags and Novelty workers Union, Local 1, and New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Ass., and Jade Handbag, Inc., 1983 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Leather Goods, Plastics, Handbags and Novelty workers Union, Local 1, and NY Industrial council of the National Handbag Ass. And Jean Fogel Creations, Inc. Gloria Contreras, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Leather Goods, Plastics, Handbags and Novelty workers Union, Local 1, and NY Industrial Council of the National Handbag Ass. And Lewis Purses, Inc., 1983 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Leather Goods, Plastics, Handbags and Novelty workers Union, Local 1, and NY Industrial Council of the Nat'l Handbag Ass. And Mac Originals, Inc. Clara Rivera, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- American League of Professional Baseball Clubs and The National League of Professional Baseball Clubs and Major League Baseball Players Association, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Manhattan Rubber workers Independent Union and Manhattan Rubber Division, Raybestos - Manhattan, Inc., 1962 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  Dec 27
- Manhattan Rubber Workers Independent Union, Inc. and Manhattan Rubber Division, Raybestos-Manhattan Inc. John Stangl, 1963 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- National Football League and NFL Players Association Room and Board Grievance, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- NFL 1971 Injury Grievance Claims, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- NFL 1971 Injury Grievance Claim, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- NFLPA and NFL Management Council, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Wendell Tucker and Miami Dolphins, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- NFLPA and NFL Player Relations Association and Members of the NFL, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- NFLPA and NFL Relations Association rules of Procedure (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America and Allied Tankers, Inc., 1971 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- Brotherhood of Marine Officers, Nat'l Maritime Union, and Amer. Export and Isbrandsten Lines Charles Matthews, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- Brotherhood of Marine Officers, Nat'l Maritime Union, and Amer. Export and Isbrantsen Lines, John Lynch, et al. (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America, and Amer. Export Isbrantsen Lines Prine Williams, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  Aug. 12
- Brotherhood of Marine Officers, Nat'l Maritime Union, and Amer. Export Isbrantsen Lines, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 22)
- Nat'l Maritime Union and Amer. Export Isbrantsen Lines Sidney Rubenstein, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 23)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America and American Export Isbrantsen Lines, Inc. Claude Russell, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 24)
- Nat'l Maritime Union and Amer. Export Isbrantsen Lines, Ed Verdi, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 25)
- National Maritime Union of America and American Export Isbrantsen Lines, Inc., 1971 (Box 25, Folder 26)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America and Amer. Export Isbrantsen Lines, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  Aug. 26
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America and Amer. Export Isbrantsen Lines Calvin Johnson, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 28)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of Amer. Merchant Marine Institute, Comm. For Companies and agents (Atlantic Gulf Coasts) on Behalf of Grace Line, Inc., 1962 (Box 25, Folder 29)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of Amer. Merchant Marine Institute, Comm. For Companies and Agents (Atlantic & Gulf coasts), 1962 (Box 25, Folder 30)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of Amer. Merchant Marine Institute, Comm. For Companies and Agents (Atlantic and gulf Coasts) and behalf of Farnell Lines, Inc. (Box 25, Folder 31)
- Nat'l Maritime Union and Amer. Merchant Marine Institute, comm. For companies & Agents (Atlantic & Gulf coasts)) and Behalf of Grace Line, Inc. Roger Chipman, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 32)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of Amer. Merchant Marine Institute, Committee for Companies and Agents (Atlantic and Gulf coasts) on Behalf of United States Lines, Inc. Curtis Jackson, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 33)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of Amer. Merchant Marine Institute, Committee For Companies and Agents (Atlantic & Gulf Coasts) on Behalf of Amer. Export Isbrantsen Lines, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 34)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of Amer. Merchant Marine Institute, committee For companies and Agents (Atlantic and Gulf Ports), on Behalf of the Gulf and South American Steamship Company, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  March 15
- Nat'l Maritime Union of Amer. Merchant Marine Institute, comm. For companies and Agents (Atlantic and Gulf coasts), 1965 (Box 25, Folder 36)
- Nat'l Maritime Union and Amer. Oil company William Christy, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 37)
- Nat'l Maritime Union and American Trading and Production William Broan, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 38)
- Nat'l Maritime Union and American Trading and Production Corp. Brown, William, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 39)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America and American Shipping Corp., 1971 (Box 25, Folder 40)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America and Americargo Shipping corp., 1972 (Box 25, Folder 41)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America and commerce Tankers Corp., 1971 (Box 25, Folder 42)
- Nat'l Maritime Union and Doric Shipping and Trading Corp., 1972 (Box 25, Folder 43)
  Jan 17
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America and Earl J Smith Andres Hall, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 44)
- Nat'l Maritime Union and Eastmount Shipping Corp., 1972 (Box 25, Folder 45)
- Nat'l Maritime Union and Farrell Lines, Inc., 1970 (Box 25, Folder 46)
- Nat'l Maritime Union and Farrell Lines Leroy Clay, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 47)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America and Freighters, Inc., 1972 (Box 25, Folder 48)
- Nat'l Maritime Union and Grace Line, Inc. Pablo Rodriguez, et al., 1967 (Box 25, Folder 49)
  Dec 20
- Nat'l Maritime and Grace lines, Inc. Ruth Weintraub, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 50)
- Nat'l Maritime Union and Grace Inc. Socorro Lopez, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 51)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America and gulf Oil Company, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 52)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America and Gulf Oil company, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 53)
- 1972 (Box 25, Folder 54)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America and Gulf Oil Company, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 55)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America, and Intercoastal Shipping and Trading Corp., 1972 (Box 25, Folder 56)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America and Linwood Shipping Corp., 1972 (Box 25, Folder 57)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America and Maritime Service comm, Inc. (On behalf of Grace Lines, Inc.), 1969 (Box 25, Folder 58)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America and Mathiasen's tanker Industries Francisco Pereira, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 59)
  may 12
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America and Mathiasen Tankers Industries Francisco Pereira, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 60)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America, and Moore-McCormack lines John Kadash, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 61)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America, and Moore - McCormack Lines Pearlie Kato, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 62)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America and Moore-McCormack Lines George Corisine, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 63)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America, and Moore-McCormack Lines George Corisine, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 64)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America, and Moore-McCormack Lines, Wilfred Nelson, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 65)
- National Maritime Union of America and Moore-McCormack Lines, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 66)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America and Moore-McCormack Lines, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 67)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America and Moore-McCormack Lines, Inc., 1973 (Box 25, Folder 68)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America, and Moore-McCormack Lines, Inc., 1973 (Box 25, Folder 69)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America and Mutual Steamship Company, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 70)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America, and People to People Health Foundation, Roberto Ramirez, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 71)
  May 29
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America, and People to People Health Foundation Roberto Ramirez, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 72)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America, and Pocahontas Steamship company, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 73)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America and Prudential - Grace Lines, Inc. Luis v. Bonilla, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 74)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America and Prudential - Grace Lines, Inc. Ellis Jefferson, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 75)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America, and Prudential - Grace Lines, Inc. Marjorie Newson, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 76)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America, and Prudential - Grace Lines, Inc. Secora Rodriguez, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 77)
- Nat'l Maritime Union and Prudential Graces Lines, Inc. Enrique Quintero, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 78)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America, and Prudential -Grace Lines Roberto Ramirez, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 79)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America and Prudential Grace Steamship company, Miguel Williams, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 80)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America and Red Ball SSCO, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 81)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America, and Spending SS and Trading Corp., 1972 (Box 25, Folder 82)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America, and State Marine Lines, Inc., 1965 (Box 25, Folder 83)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America, and States Marine Lines, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 84)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America and Tanker Service Comm. (On behalf of Texaco) Russell Miller, et al., 1963 (Box 25, Folder 85)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America and Tanker Service Comm. (on behalf of Texaco), 1963 (Box 25, Folder 86)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America and tanker Service Comm. (On behalf of Texaco), 1963 (Box 25, Folder 87)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America and Tanker Service comm. (on behalf of Texaco), 1963 (Box 25, Folder 88)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America, and Tanker Service Comm. (on behalf of Sinclair Refining Comp.) Water Peck, 1963 (Box 25, Folder 89)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America and Tanker Service Comm. (On behalf of Texaco), 1963 (Box 25, Folder 90)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America, and Tanker Service comm. (On behalf of Sinclair) Refining Company John Henderson, 1963 (Box 25, Folder 91)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America, and tanker Service comm. (on behalf of Texaco), 1963 (Box 25, Folder 92)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America, and tanker Service comm.(on behalf of Sinclair Refining Comp.) Walter Pack, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 93)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America, and tanker Service comm., Inc. (on behalf of Sinclair Refining Co.) L Fondananova, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 94)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America, and tanker Service comm. (On behalf of Texaco), 1964 (Box 25, Folder 95)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America, and tanker Service comm. (on behalf of Texaco), 1964 (Box 25, Folder 96)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America, and tanker Service comm. (on behalf of Texaco) M N Woolley, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 97)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America, and tanker Service comm. (on behalf of Sinclair Refining Comp. and Texaco, Inc.) Albert Romer, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 98)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America, and tanker Service comm. (on behalf of Texaco), 1969 (Box 25, Folder 99)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America, and Terrace Navigation Corp., 1972 (Box 25, Folder 100)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America, and Trans American Trailer Transport, Inc. William Meakens, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 101)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America, and Trans-America Trailer Transport, Inc. William Meakens, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 102)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America and Transoceanic Enterprise Corp., 1972 (Box 25, Folder 103)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America and Trinidad Corp. Santos Montalbo, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 104)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America, and U.S. Lines, Inc., 1963 (Box 25, Folder 105)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America and US Lines Comp. Gaston Firmin - guyon, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 106)
  Oct 22
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America, and US Lines Inc. Raphael Charles, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 107)
  Oct 21
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America and US Lines, Inc. Pauline Dziob, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 108)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America US Lines, Inc., 1971 (Box 25, Folder 109)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America, and US Lines, Inc. Lewis Savoia, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 110)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America, and US Lines, Inc. Frank Liberatore, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 111)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America, and US Lines Inc., Edward Harris, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 112)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America, and US Lines Inc. Tomas Townes, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 113)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America and Westbury Steamship Co., 1972 (Box 25, Folder 114)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America, and Wilton Shipping Corp., 1972 (Box 25, Folder 115)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America and Grace Line, Inc. and Amer. Export Isbrantsen Lines, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 116)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America Export Isbrantsen Lines, Inc. and US Lines, Inc., 1970 (Box 25, Folder 117)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America Export Isbrantsen Lines and US Lines, Inc., 1970 (Box 25, Folder 118)
- Nat'l Maritime Union of America and various companies and Agents (Atlantic and Gulf Coasts), 1958 (Box 25, Folder 119)
- Newspaper and Mail Deliverers Union and Imperial News company, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 120)
- American Newspaper Guild, AFL-CIO, Newspaper Guild of NY, and Free Europe Committee, Inc., 1958 (Box 25, Folder 121)
- And. Newspaper Guild of NY, and Free Europe Committee, Inc. Shefki Miraka, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 122)
  March 14
- Newspaper Guild of NY and NYT Comp. Frank Nania, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 123)
- NYT Company and Newspaper guild of NY, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 124)
- NYT Comp. and Newspaper Guild of NY, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 125)
- Parade Publications, Inc., and Newspaper Guild of NY, Local 3 James B. Golden, et al., 1949 (Box 25, Folder 126)
- Newspaper Guild of New York and New York News, Inc., 1978 (Box 25, Folder 127)
- Newspaper guild of New York and New York Post corporation, 1973-1975 (Box 25, Folder 128)
  March 31, 1973 - March 30, 1975
- Brewers Board of Trade for Member Piel Brothers, and NY Brewery Workers Joint board Locals 124 and 1345, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 129)
- New York Mailer's Union and New York Daily News, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- NY Mailer's Union #6 and NY Post Corp., 1971 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- NY Mailers Union No. 6 and NY Post Frank Bragoli, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- New York times and New York Mailers Union No. 6, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- New York Mailer's Union No. 6 and Publishers' Association of New York City, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- NY News, Inc. and NY Times Company, and NY Mailers' Union No. 6, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- New York Newspaper and Mail deliverer's Union, and NY Times, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- New York Newspaper Printing Pressmen's Union No. 2 and New York News, Inc., 1977 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- New York Newspaper Printing Pressmen's Union No. 2 and The New York times Company, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  March 14-16
- New York Newspaper Printing Pressmen's Union No. 2 and The Publishers' Association of New York City, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  March 31, 1975 - March 30
- NY Paper Cutters' and Bookbinders' Union 119 and Printer's League Section, Printing Industries at Metropolitan New York, Inc., 1964 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- NY Paper Cutters' and bookbinders' Union 119 and Printers League Section, Printing Industries of Metropolitan NY, Inc., 1964 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- NY Paper Cutters' and bookbinders' Union 119 and Printers League Section, Printing Industries of Metropolitan NY, Inc., 1964 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- NY Paper Cutters' and bookbinders' Union 119 and Printers League Section, Printing Industries of Metropolitan NY, Inc., 1965 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- NY Paper Cutters' and bookbinders' Union 119 and US Printing and Lithograph division of diamond Nat'l corp., 1965 (Box 26, Folder 15)
- Drafts - NY Typographical Union No. 8 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- Misc. -- NY Typographical Union No. 6 (Box 26, Folder 17)
- Kheel - Personal Notes (Box 26, Folder 18)
- NY Typographical Union No. 6, and NY Herald Tribune William Schlosses, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 19)